<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>Padmanaba Srinivasan</title>
    
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Behavioral Supervisor Tuning</title>
        <description>
          
          Conferences confine a paper to be at most X pages in length, where X is usually 7-10 pages. The need to communicate most of the important (theoretical and experimental) parts of my work in such a format means making sacrifices - this often ends in me removing text that aims...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-03-04-tech-blog-Behavioral-Supervisor-Tuning/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-03-04-tech-blog-Behavioral-Supervisor-Tuning/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thoughts on DPO and Offline RL</title>
        <description>
          
          Direct Preference Optimization is all the rage now in LLMs, and rightly so! The derivation is neat (and very familiar to those experienced with reinforcement learning) and allows direct, preference-based finetuning of regression-trained LLMs without having to learn a reward model. In this post, I want to explore what implications...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-06-22-tech-blog-Thoughts-On-DPO-and-Offline-RL/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-06-22-tech-blog-Thoughts-On-DPO-and-Offline-RL/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some Interesting Offline RL Methods (Early 2024)</title>
        <description>
          
          Intro Reinforcement Learning (RL) combined with deep learning has shown incredible promise in recent years: in 2016, AlphaGo was good enough to beat the best Go players; by 2017 AlphaGo Zero learned to play against itself and blew AlphaGo’s performance out of the water; and in 2019 MuZero mastered not...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-02-22-tech-blog-Some-Interesting-Offline-RL-Methods-Early-2024/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-02-22-tech-blog-Some-Interesting-Offline-RL-Methods-Early-2024/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Introduction to Preference-Based RL</title>
        <description>
          
          Intro In Reinforcement Learning (RL), an agent navigates through an environment and learns to maximize a discounted sum of scalar rewards produced as a property of the environment. In practice, however, no environment decides to provide a reward signal – such signals are the product of human design. At its...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-02-22-tech-blog-An-Introduction-to-Preference-Based-RL/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-02-22-tech-blog-An-Introduction-to-Preference-Based-RL/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Overview of Model-Based Offline RL Methods</title>
        <description>
          
          Intro Model-Free vs Model-Based RL In Reinforcement Learning (RL) tasks, an agent interacts with an environment by executing an action, a, given the current state, s and transitions to the next state s’ defined by the environment. The environment yields a scalar reward r at transition which, with successive interaction,...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-02-22-tech-blog-A-Overview-of-Model-Based-Offline-RL/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-02-22-tech-blog-A-Overview-of-Model-Based-Offline-RL/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Intro to Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
        <description>
          
          What is Reinforcement Learning? Say you have bought a table from a certain Swedish retailer famous for both their fairly priced furnite, and meatballs, but have lost the instructions to assemble it. A trivial, albeit cumbersome approach would be to just try putting different parts together and to make it...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2023-12-15-tech-blog-An-Intro-to-Offline-Reinforcement-Learning/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2023-12-15-tech-blog-An-Intro-to-Offline-Reinforcement-Learning/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
